<?xml version="1.0"?>
<FlipbookData>
    <Settings ZoomFactor="2.5" PageScale="true" ThumbWidth="223" ThumbHeight="288" PageWidth="330" PageHeight="427" StartPage="1" navBar="true" Hardcover="false" Hardpage="false" EmbossedPages="true" EmbossAlpha="100" ClickArea="15" GotoPageSpeed="4" RightToLeft="false" PageCache="4" UnloadPages="true" PageLoaderBackColor="0xFFFFFF" PageBgColor="0xa6a6a6" BackgroundImageFile="" PageLoaderColor="0x666666" IconColor="0xcccccc" IconOverColor="0xffffff" ControlBgColor="0x101010" PagerColor="0xcccccc" PopupColor="0x121212" PrintPopupTextColor="0xcccccc" PDFlink="ffdd8c7906.pdf" SearchPages="true" PrintPages="true" PdfLoad="true" CenterSinglePage="true" FadeLinks="true" ShowLinkToolTips="true" ToolTipColor="0x333333" ToolTipTextColor="0xffffff" searchboxTextColor="0x666666" linkColor="0x0000ff" ShadowsEnabled="true" ShadowsAlpha="85" PagesHaveShadow="false" PageShadowSize="15" PageShadowOffset="2" PageShadowAlpha="40" transparentLinks="true" zoomIconColor="0x222222" ZoomPages="true" thumbIndex="true" showFullscreen="true" soundsEnabled="true" BookMarginVertical="25" BookMarginHorizontal="25" StartAutoFlip="false" AutoFlipDefaultInterval="6000" AutoFlipLooping="true"/>
    <Pages>
                    <Page HighRes="page1.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page1.jpg"><text>BRINGING LIFE INTO FOCUS </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page2.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page2.jpg"><text>Finding a retirement plan solution that ts your needs and the needs of your employees while maintaining a costbenet structure is a daunting task not to mention nding a solution that is easy to understand and compliant. Stop and allow yourself to take a deep breath and think of the weight of the responsibilities that you bear as the owner of a business or senior manager of a business. You are focusing on expanding revenues. Are you recognizing your best contributors Are you offering the most competitive benets package to retain or recruit talent Are you getting the best and most cost-effective benets Are you complying with the myriad of regulations regarding your retirement plan If you answered no to any of these questions we encourage you to read on. Over the next few pages we will explore together the major obstacles faced by business owners and senior managers like yourself and how the iCM Retirement Plan program has helped them to focus their energies on revenue-producing activities that should be driving your daily schedule and not worry about your retirement plan. We encourage each of our plan sponsor partners to continue to strive for excellence in their business and leave the retirement plan solutions to us. 1 Easy to offer with little administrative burden. 2 Cost-effective and designed to meet your unique needs. 3 Compliant with industry rules  regulations including ERISA 404a and 408b2. 4 Quality name-brand fund line up. Compliance is a partnership. Our plans are designed to make compliance simple. Compliance is not guaranteed without your participation. We cannot attest to nor be responsible for plan sponsor responsibilities included but not limited to timely remittance of contributions or failure to distribute participant notices. Benets of an iCM Retirement Plan </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page3.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page3.jpg"><text>Easy to Offer A common concern among employers who know they need a retirement plan as part of their benets package is the additional burden that may be placed on their staff. By offering an iCM retirement plan we do the heavy lifting so that you can focus on what you do bestmanaging your business and its future growth. Whether your needs require a fully bundled turn-key solution that integrates recordkeeping TPA  investment services or an  la carte solution were uniquely suited to meet your needs.  Hands-off total portfolio management solutions for participants at no additional cost.1  Ongoing professional oversight and management as a 338 Fiduciary for both the risk-based investment models and full fund lineup.  Easy-to-use platform for retirement savings.  Production of quarterly research materials to aid DOL review requirements.  Employee Meetings and Participant Education.  Annual Testing  Reporting.2  Independent custody of assets daily valuation  recordkeeping plus administrative services.2 What we do for you  Timely remittance of participant contributions and matched dollars.  Deliver iCM created plan communications to employees if necessary.  Dedicate your energies to your business and let iCM handle the rest. Plan Sponsor Responsibilities 1 1 iCM charges one comprehensive fee. Portfolio management solutions are included in the comprehensive fee. 2 iCM partners with leading Third-Party Administrator and recordkeeping rms for full service offerings. </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page4.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page4.jpg"><text>2 Cost-Effective Solutions Any time the discussion of an employee benet is broached it typically comes with a discussion on cost. The retirement plan landscape is riddled with land mines ranging from complicated share class structures to platform fees and contract charges. Most have one goal in mind to make it seem like you are paying less than you are for a retirement offering. Were Different. With iCM you can rest easy knowing that full 338 duciary services for investment models and a complete fund line up are included in our offer. iCM bundles the 338 duciary services and plan provider expenses which are typically offered by separate providers. By eliminating an additional layer of cost iCM provides a comprehensive retirement plan solution at a more effective price point. </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page5.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page5.jpg"><text>Purchasing Power at Work  Know exactly what you are paying and what you are receiving.  Access to institutional pricing.  Our fund line up median expense ratio is 63 less than the Morningstar category average. Data as of 9302015 - </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page6.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page6.jpg"><text>Compliant One of the greatest challenges faced by a plan sponsor is guring out who is ultimately responsible. In a word the answer is you When you consider an overwhelming majority of all lawsuits are caused by a retirement plan issue related to a breach of duciary duty it is of the utmost importance that you partner with a team that takes the details seriously. In an effort to limit liability a retirement plan should include several components that aid a plan sponsor in delivering a more compliant offering. This begins with an ERISA 338 duciary like iCM. Hiring a consultant who makes recommendations that you must approve is simply not enough. The act of approving the recommendation makes you responsible When working with a 338 duciary like iCM we keep you informed but will never ask you to make an investment decision. Thats our job. Helping you to be Compliant  Safe  338 duciary services covering model portfolios and fund line up. Most 338s only cover their model portfolios leaving you exposed.  Online access for booking contributions help you remain in compliance with the DOL denition of Timely Remittance. Seamless TPA integration for accurate plan testing and future design.  Compliance for plan document drafting and required EGGTRA updates.  Quarterly investment review booklet Retire Tracs documenting DOL Plan Sponsor supervisory requirements. By working with iCM we make it easy for you to offer a sensible retirement solution that is compliant with the changing regulatory landscape. 3 Source- 2009 Pension Governance Inc. and The Michel-Shaked Group Study </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page7.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page7.jpg"><text>338 vs Other Fiduciaries ERISA Section 321 ERISA Section 321  Denes the broad duties of a plan duciary. For the purposes of investment selection ERISA allows for Plan Sponsors to complete their Plans investment selection on their own or hire an advisor or investment manager to assist them by providing suggestions analysis reports andor specialized tools. These advisors and investment managers are considered to be Section 321 co-duciaries. While the advisor and investment manager serve as co-duciaries this does not relieve the Plan Sponsor of its duciary responsibility for the selection and monitoring of the investments offered within the Plan. These advisors are only responsible for the suggestions they make and the analysis they provide. They are not responsible for the ultimate outcomes since the Plan Sponsor still maintains nal decision making authority and ultimately the liability that goes with it. ERISA Section 338 Under this arrangement an investment manager accepts authority to manage acquire and dispose of investment options. The investment manager acknowledges in writing that they are a duciary with responsibility and accountability for the selection of the investments offered within the Plan. ERISA Section 405d provides that under a 338 arrangement the Plan Sponsor andor Trustees of the Plan are not liable for acts or omissions of the 338 investment manager and are under no obligation to any investment or to otherwise manage any asset of the plan which is subject to the management of that investment manager. A 338 arrangement represents the highest level of investment liability transfer possible under ERISA from the plan sponsor to the investment manager. </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page8.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page8.jpg"><text>Quality Solutions that are Easy for Participants Have we mentioned that its easy to offer an iCM retirement plan Its even easier for your participants. There are typically two investment personalities. Type A Do it yourself and Type B We do it for you. In either case all investment options have undergone extensive due diligence aka quality control by our investment team. Type A In the Do It Yourself option the participant can select their own funds from a menu of 30-50 options. These options range from traditional asset class offerings to sector funds and even liquid alternatives.  Full fund line up of 30-50 brand name mutual funds for the do-it-yourselfers  Online access for participants providing timely investment and account information account rebalance options and service requests. Type B In the Let Us Do It option participants can complete a short risk prole questionnaire then sit back and leave the driving to us. We manage everything from fund selection to asset allocation. The best part we do it for you at no additional cost.1  Risk-based model portfolios managed by iCM and available at no additional cost.  Online access for participants providing timely investment and account information account rebalance options and service requests. Are you Type A who would prefer to do it yourself or Type B who would like us to do it We have you covered either way TYPE B Let Us Do It 1. Complete a Risk Questionnaire. 2. The scoring directs you to a pre-mixed model portfolio. 3. iCM does everything for you including choosing the funds and the asset mix for your strategy. 4. No additional cost1 TYPE A Do It Yourself 1. Pre-screened fund line up of 30-50 brand name funds including the major asset classes sectors and liquid alternatives. 2. iCM research including fund fact sheets. 3. Morningstar Research. 4. No trading costs 4 1 iCM charges one comprehensive fee. Portfolio management solutions are included in the comprehensive fee. </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page9.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page9.jpg"><text>About iCM The Benets of an iCM Retirement Plan Include  Professional management and oversight. ERISA 338 duciary status on both investment models and full fund lineup at one low cost.  All-inclusive fee-based pricing available.  Independent custody record-keeping and real-time reporting.  Online account access with daily valuation for participants and plan sponsors.  Quarterly research and investment insights intended to satisfy DOL due diligence requirements and employee education. onal management and oversight. ERISA 338 duciary both investment models and full fund lineup at one low cost. sive fee-based pricing available. dent custody record-keeping and real-time reporting. account access with daily valuation for participants n sponsors. y research and investment insights intended to satisfy e diligence requirements and employee education. Valuations Drive Returns The term valuations typically refers to the price of a stock or of any group of stocks relativeThe term valuations typically refers to the price of a stock or of any group of stocks relative to the earnings of the company or companies that issued the stock. We believe what isto the earnings of the company or companies that issued the stock. We believe what is important from an investment perspective is valuations drive returns. While fear and greed canimportant from an investment perspective is valuations drive returns. While fear and greed can push an entire class of stocks e.g. large-cap growth small-cap growth above or below itspush an entire class of stocks e.g. large-cap growth small-cap growth above or below its long-term fair value in the short-term our research has shown that over longer periods marketslong-term fair value in the short-term our research has shown that over longer periods markets inevitably nd their way back to normal fair value. Since we design our portfolios for long-terminevitably nd their way back to normal fair value. Since we design our portfolios for long-term results we place a great emphasis on relative valuations in determining the allocation to eachresults we place a great emphasis on relative valuations in determining the allocation to each class of stocks within each portfolio.class of stocks within each portfolio. </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page10.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page10.jpg"><text>Retirement Plan Options Many retirement plan options exist within the current landscape. Finding the right plan or combination of plans is a very personal decision. Dont become overwhelmed. In partnership with your nancial advisor we will design a retirement plan structure that is right for you. Some things to keep in mind when making retirement plan decisions  Ownership structure of the business.  Corporate structure of the business.  What is your ideal nancial contribution to your employees  OwnerSenior Management deferral options.  Number of current employees.  Are you expecting to expand your workforce  Do you have a current plan for your business  Does your business have unique needs or a non-traditional workforce 401k Money Purchase Pension  Most common retirement plan designed with for-prot businesses in mind.  Designated Roth Account Option.  Safe Harbor.  Prot Sharing. 403b Plan  Designed for not-for-prot enterprises charities churches hospitals.  Designated Roth Account Option. 457 Plan  Designed for state and local government employees. Cash Balance Plans  Designed for closely held businessprofessional practices - medical groups law practices accounting rms.  Form of dened benet retirement plan. All retirement plans with iCM are fully customizable to serve the unique needs of each business. </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page11.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page11.jpg"><text>DISCLOSURE Integrated Capital Management iCM is registered with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission SEC as an investment adviser. Registration with the SEC does not imply any certain level of skill or training. Investors should note that there are risks inherent in all investments including the possible loss of all amounts invested. Past performance of any index investment or strategy is not indicative of future returns and should not be relied upon as a guarantee of future results. There is no guarantee that a diversied portfolio will outperform a non-diversied portfolio in any given market environment. No investment strategy can guarantee prot or protection against loss in periods of declining values. Sponsors of 401k plans and other types of dened contribution retirement plans with participant-directed investments are subject to the Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974 as amended ERISA as well as the service providers that work with such plans. iCM will comply in all respects with its respective duciary obligations under ERISA including but not limited to the obligation a to act with the care skill prudence and diligence under the circumstances then prevailing that a prudent man acting in a like capacity and familiar with such matters would use in the conduct of an enterprise of a like character and with like aims and b to avoid causing any such Fund it manages Fund to engage in any non-exempt prohibited transactions under Section 406 of ERISA and Section 4975 of the Code. iCM has notice led to conduct advisory services in numerous states. For a complete listing please refer to our form ADV Part 2 at www.icm-invest.com. This brochure does not constitute an offer to sell a solicitation of an offer to buy or a recommendation of any security or any other product or service by iCM in states not listed. If you are interested in iCMs advisory services and reside in a state other than the listed states please contact iCM so we may begin the notication process in order to discuss with you our advisory services. Past performance of investments may not be indicative of future results or investments. Any investment strategy is subject to various factors including but not limited to general and local economic conditions changing levels of competition within certain industries and markets changes in interest rates changes in legislation or regulation and other economic competitive governmental regulatory and technological factors affecting iCMs operations that could cause actual results to differ materially from projected results. This brochure does not constitute a recommendation or solicitation to buy or an offer to sell any security or investment product mentioned in this document. Please refer to our Form ADV Part 2A for more information. </text></Page>
                <Page HighRes="page12.swf" Thumbnail="thumbnails/page12.jpg"><text>410 Spruce Street Scranton PA 18503 Toll-Free 888 426-4689 www.icm-invest.com </text></Page>
                </Pages>
    <PageLinks>
                        <PageLink linkID="" pageID="11" tooltip="Click to open this link" link="http://www.icm-invest.com." linkType="external" linkTarget="_blank" x="138.4434" y="329.9738" width="97.207" height="13.893"/>
                    <PageLink linkID="" pageID="12" tooltip="Click to open this link" link="http://www.icm-invest.com" linkType="external" linkTarget="_blank" x="216.2454" y="505.1335" width="179.5101" height="26.523"/>
                </PageLinks>
    <YoutubeVideos/>
    
<Language PagerText="#" DownloadText="Download PDF" IndexText="Thumbnail Index" FullscreenText="Open Fullscreen" ExitFullscreenText="" PrintText="Print Pages" FirstPageText="First Page" LastPageText="Last Page" PreviousPageText="Previous Page" NextPageText="Next Page" SearchText="Search" SearchHintText="Search publication.."/></FlipbookData>
